I didn't touch your brother.
أنا لم ألمس أخيك.
I didn't hurt him.
أنا لم أؤذيه.
I didn't scare him.
أنا لم أخافه.
It's true.
انها حقيقة.
I didn't take you down.
أنا لم أنزلك.
To bring it to the imperial court,
لإحضاره إلى البلاط الإمبراطوري ،
it's already the greatest tolerance for you.
إنه بالفعل أكبر تسامح بالنسبة لك.
Don't push your luck.
لا تدفع حظك.
What do you have to do to forgive me
ماذا عليك أن تفعل لتسامحني
and leave my sight.
واترك بصري.
Don't let me see you again.
لا تدعني أراك مرة أخرى.
It's you. You
انه انت.  أنت
didn't expect it, did you?
لم تتوقعها ، أليس كذلك؟
I'll take you down one day.
سآخذك يوما ما.
You should be glad that I don't want to kill you yet.
يجب أن تكون سعيدًا لأنني لا أريد قتلك بعد.
Why?
لماذا؟
Could it be
هل من الممكن ذلك
Is it because of your mother Yanchu?
هل هو بسبب والدتك يانشو؟
What did you do to my mother?
ماذا فعلت لأمي؟
Your mother,
أمك،
I really love you.
أنا حقا أحبك.
Even if I cut off the fins,
حتى لو قطعت الزعانف
he still refuses to tell the truth.
لا يزال يرفض قول الحقيقة.
You merman jerks
أنت الحمقى حوري البحر
are really useless.
هي حقا عديمة الفائدة.
You,
أنت،
If you're sensible,
إذا كنت عاقلًا ،
just let me go.
فقط دعني اذهب.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
I can't guarantee that Yanchu
لا أستطيع أن أضمن أن يانتشو
will be safe and sound.
ستكون آمنة وسليمة.
I told you to leave but you really did.
أخبرتك أن تغادر لكنك فعلت ذلك حقًا.
Stinky salted fish,
السمك المملح نتن ،
you didn't come to me even when you were in heat.
أنت لم تأت إلي حتى عندما كنت في الحر.
Drink my blood.
اشرب دمي.
You won't have to work for others anymore.
لن تضطر إلى العمل مع الآخرين بعد الآن.
Well
حسنًا
It's your turn to speak.
حان دورك للتحدث.
Can Gu Danmo give you any benefit after the job is done?
هل يمكن أن يمنحك Gu Danmo أي فائدة بعد انتهاء العمل؟
Senior Tutor wants to take over the people of the world,
يريد كبير المدرسين تولي مسؤولية الناس في العالم ،
how can you speculate here?
كيف يمكنك التكهن هنا؟